Something crooked this way comes.
Hellboy: The Crooked Man is a fantasy, horror,
action film directed by Brian Taylor.
Hellboy and a rookie BPRD agent get stranded in 1950s rural Appalachia.
There, they discover a small community haunted by witches, led by a local devil
with a troubling connection to Hellboy's past: the Crooked Man.
Hellboy, played by Jack Kesy.
Tom Ferrell, played by Jefferson White.
Bobbie Jo Song, played by Adeline Rudolph.
Effie Kolb, played by Leah McNamara.
Cora Fisher, played by Hannah Margetson.
The Crooked Man, played by Martin Bassindale.
Hellboy: The Crooked Man is a 2024 American superhero horror film, based on the
Dark Horse Comics character Hellboy created by Mike Mignola.
Produced by Millennium Media, Dark Horse Entertainment, Nu Boyana Film Studios, and Campbell Grobman Films, it is
the second reboot of the Hellboy film series and is the fourth live-action entry in the franchise.
It is directed by Brian Taylor from a script he wrote with Mignola and Christopher
Golden, adapting The Crooked Man limited series written by Mignola.
The film stars Jack Kesy as Hellboy, alongside Jefferson
White and Adeline Rudolph in her film debut.
Filming began in March 2023, in Bulgaria, and was completed in May.
Hellboy: The Crooked Man was released in Belgium on June 20, 2024, and was released
direct-to-VOD in the United States by Ketchup Entertainment on October 8, 2024.
The film received mixed reviews from critics and has
grossed $2 million in international markets.
The film explores themes of witch, spider, based on comic, coal mine, 1950s.
The tone is dark.